<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide Application</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="lake_name1">Prashar Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_name2">Serolsar Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_name3">Chandra Taal Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_name4">Bhrigu_Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_description1">The lake is located at a height of 2730 m above sea level. With
        deep blue waters, the lake is held sacred to the sage Prashar and he is regarded to have
        meditated there. Surrounded by snow-capped peaks and looking down on the fast flowing river
        Beas, the lake can be approached via Drang. There is a round, floating island inside the
        lake, which is a common natural phenomenon found all around the world.</string>
    <string name="lake_description2">Serolsar Lake is located at an altitude of 3199 m. It is
        surrounded by thick vegetation of alpine forests. There is a myth that even if a small leaf
        falls into the Lake the birds around takes them out of the lake and keeps the water crystal
        clear. The water of the lake is believed to have medicinal properties.</string>
    <string name="lake_description3">Chandra Taal lake is on the Samudra Tapu plateau,which overlooks
        Chandra river (a source river of the Chenab). The name of the lake originates from its crescent
        shape. It is at an altitude of about 4,300 metres (14,100 ft)in the Himalayas.Mountains of scree
        overlook the lake on one side, and a cirque encloses it on the other.</string>
    <string name="lake_description4">Bhrigu Lake or Brighu Lake is a lake located at an elevation of
        around 4,300 metres (14,100 ft) in Kullu district, Himachal Pradesh, India. It is located to
        the east of Rohtang Pass and is around 6 kilometres (3.7 mi) from Gulaba village. It can be
        reached by trekking either from the Vashishth temple, which is famous for its hot water
        springs, close to the town of Manali. Actually there is no settlement in Gulaba and is an
        area of the Pir Panjal mountain range. It is named after Maharishi Bhrigu.</string>
</resources>
